Okay, if Leonard has problems with me,
why hasn't he just said so?
(Sheldon:)According to him, you're over-sensitive
and have a temper.
Oh, really? Well, then do me a favor
and tell Leonard that he can drop dead.
(Sheldon:)And she wonders
why she's constantly under-tipped.
(Penny:)-Hey.
-Oh, good, you're home.
-I need you to do me a favor.
-Sure.
(Sheldon:)-Go apologize to Penny.
-What?
(Sheldon:)Right now would be good.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
PENNY: Leonard!
-A few minutes ago would've been better.
(Penny:)I hear you don't like my stuffed animals,
my driving or my punctuality.
(Leonard:)Who would tell you
something like that?
(Leonard:)Why would you tell her
(Penny:)It doesn't matter why he told me.
It's true, isn't it?
(Leonard:)Okay, yeah, it's true.
But I can live with that stuff.
(Leonard:)What I can't live with
is you casually informing me...
...some guy is gonna be staying
without asking me first.
(Penny:)That isn't even your problem.
Problem is you don't trust me.
(Leonard:)Oh, come on.